Welcome to the new feature introduction video of Marvelous Designer 2025.
In the current version, we have updated the user interface and increased the response speed.
First, let's take a look at the current window composition.
At the top, you can find the main menu.
Here, you can classify the function or tool.
On the left side of the screen is the 3D window.
Here, you can edit and adjust the 3D costume.
On the right side is the window of the 2D version.
Here, you can edit the 2D version.
On the top right is the object window.
Here, you can select various elements in the 3D window.
For example, plants, stickers, names, buttons, etc.
Below is the property editor.
In the property editor, you can adjust the properties of the selected items.
Click on the arrow at the bottom to open the animation editor.
Click on the button to move the animation editor window freely.
Click on the magnification icon to expand the animation editor to full screen.
Click on the small button to extend the animation editor to the previous size.
Click on the icon to close the window and return the window to its original position.
Click on the button to close the window.
These attached windows can be folded, separated, or rearranged.
In the lower right corner, you can switch to the main window layout or select only the 3D window or 2D window.
Click Reset to reset the page to default layout.
Now, in the 2025 version, you can manage all windows at the bottom of the window bar.
You can choose whether to display these windows.
If you need to open a window, you can go to the menu below to select the corresponding option.
In this menu, there is a interface layout option that allows you to export and switch between different page layout options.
The export page layout can be switched in the top row of the layout option bar.
Then, let's take a look at the updated main menu.
Two new main menus have been added.
The third menu is the
Set the default layout to the default layout in the user's definition.
There is a high-quality layout and style layout option in the layout tab.
The layout type is the same as the previous version.
You can click the corresponding icon in the 3D window to open or cancel the application.
The Everywhere function is set to the Connect tab.
You can change the layout settings here.
The layer has different options.
For example, we will choose the default layout.
To right-click and select the New Layout,
we will open the new layout window.
The new layout window shows our default assets.
When you switch to the Connects assets tabs, you will be able to directly use these commercial assets.
Click on the CLOSET tab to manage or open the files you have uploaded to the CLOSET platform.
Click on the old drawing box to return to the previous drawing box window.
Click on the new drawing box to return to the new drawing box window.
The tool icon has become larger and easier to select and use.
The tool icon has been integrated into the 3D tool box, and you do not need to change the window to use it.
Since the 2025 version, material other than fabric can also be managed in the object window.
In the scene box, you can view various components in the current project scene.
You can adjust the detail of the fabric in the plant column.
The new group system allows you to manage multiple fabrics.
You can insert, configure and manage the attached images added to the clothing in the sticker column.
In the button column, you can manage and adjust the application settings.
You can use the button type style on clothes.
You can manage and adjust the button type style on clothes in the in the button column.
In the
You can manage and adjust the attached styles applied on the clothes in the attached section.
Click on the icon window icon in the upper left corner of the label section to open the shop interface corresponding to the label section,
including the default assets and Connect shop.
For more information, please refer to our handbook page
or watch our other new feature introduction videos.
For more information, please refer to our handbook page or watch our other new feature introduction videos.